Finding Aid for the Antony Balcena Papers LSC.0625
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Videotapes
  - Music Video Choreography and Fashion Video, 1986, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Two VHS tapes. One tape is a choreography for a music video titled: Garron "Urban Gypsy" 1. Vertical 2. Horizontal [refers to camera shoots]. The second video is titled: "Life's a Beach Surfgear Fashion Video."
  - Shows Recording, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Two VHS tapes. One tape is titled: "Liza" (Naomi Simms) Re: Liza Minelli impersonation. Second tape is titled: "50's Madison-Rock-Rock." Re: excerpts of movies about the 50's music and dance.
  - Sarah Elgart & Co., 1982-1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    A KCA 30 videotape [master]. Three recording. 1) "American is Waiting" & "Crows" (1982, 1984) As performed at John Anson Ford Theatre (9:12) 2) "Marrying the Hangman" (1983) As performed at Japan American Theatre for California Olimpic Dance Festival 6/84. (11:00).
  - Choreographies, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    A KCS 20BR videotape. Video taped by Keanne Slater at Loyola Marymount College [University]. Recording titled: "Oscillate" and "No More Words."
  - Choreographies, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    KCS 20 videotape. Video titled: "Oscillate"; "Mishima--Tony"
  - Choreography Accidental Suicide, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    KCS 20BR videotape. Video titled: "Accidental Suicide."
  - The Ricardo Simmones Cho, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    KCS 20 videotape. Titled: "The Ricardo Simones Cho Antony Balcena."
  - Sarah Elgart & Co., 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    KCS 20BR videotape. It contains several musical productions: 1)"Strategies" 2)"Marrying the Hangman" 3)"Recess" 4)"Deeper Reasons," produced and performanced by the Sarah Elgart & Co.
  - Choreography The Grand Poser, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    UCA-15 videotape from Ashfield Film Lab. Film to Video. Title: "Antony Balcena 10-3-83 Antony Balcena/Choreographer Excerpts from 'The Grand Poser'"
  - Winter Dance Thesis, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    KCA 30BR videotape. Title: "Mishima" Note reads: Antony Balcena Winter Dance Thesis 1983. 485B/5965 (Clarke) 17 Minutes. Color Channel 1.
  - Lyon, Lisa, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    KCA 60BR videotape. Title: "Lisa Lyon: Live at the Laforet Museum" Note reads: Tokyo Japan Mar 29-AP 8, 1984. Contemporary Alchemy/Evolution Ritual. Tape 1.
  - Lyon, Lisa, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    KCA 60BR videotape. Title: "Lisa Lyon: Live at the Laforet Museum" Note reads: Tokyo Japan Mar 29-AP 8, 1984. Contemporary Alchemy/Evolution Ritual. Tape 2.